[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 21, "question": "Or how did that all come about?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 22, "answer": "Well, I probably thought it was kind of silly at the time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 31, "question": "Is it a hard thing to, you know, live up to all these years later?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "TO", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "RBR", "."], "aSentId": 32, "answer": "The older you get, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 64, "question": "Is it hard for you to watch?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 65, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 66, "question": "Do you watch your own movies?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 67, "answer": "Usually once.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 68, "question": "Is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 69, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 75, "question": "Is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 76, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 137, "question": "How are you dealing with all this at that time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 138, "answer": "I think it was a lot for me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 177, "question": "What are you going to torture me with now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 178, "answer": "No, no, look.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 197, "question": "You know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 198, "answer": "Right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 216, "question": "Any regrets about not taking those?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 217, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", ",", "CC", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 227, "question": "At that point were you worried about being typecast or pigeon holed in any way?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "CC", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 228, "answer": "Early on I probably was, but -- I mean that changed pretty quickly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 235, "question": "Is that OK?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 236, "answer": "OK.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 251, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 252, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 273, "question": "What'd you have to do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 274, "answer": "The whole thing was quite a task.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 281, "question": "And how long does a process like that take?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 282, "answer": "It took -- I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 300, "question": "What -- is there a key, a rule?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", ":", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 301, "answer": "Well, I think we're really compatible and just different enough to keep it interesting.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 338, "question": "Did you use him as research?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 339, "answer": "I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 345, "question": "But you know this was 1993, right, when you did this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBD", "CD", ",", "RB", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 346, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1993"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 351, "question": "I mean was it a hard decision for you to adopt, you know, unmarried?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 352, "answer": "No, not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 366, "question": "Is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 367, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 373, "question": "How could anyone be unsure about Michelle Pfeiffer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "VB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 374, "answer": "I mean, I think he was attracted to me.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michelle Pfeiffer"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 379, "question": "Who'd you get that from?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "-NONE-", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 380, "answer": "Again, we have our sources.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 410, "question": "And I -- it just really, it just really changes everything, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "NNS", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 411, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 432, "question": "Would you work with your husband?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 433, "answer": "I would be so lucky to have him be writing for me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 466, "question": "What's different about you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 467, "answer": "Really different.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 479, "question": "Is that true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 480, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "Then?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 501, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 502, "answer": "You know, I did some acupuncture.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 508, "question": "Is it something you think about?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 509, "answer": "Sometimes I do, sometimes I don't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "I mean, who cares, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "Right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 555, "question": "I mean just, the double standard that you hear about is it real?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "It is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 574, "question": "Is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 575, "answer": "I mean, I'm still -- I mean, I'm never really a glutton, you know, I mean -- I mean, in terms of relative to maybe some other people, you know...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 668, "question": "How hard is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 669, "answer": "Well, I actually really love the vegan diet because I love carbs.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "NN", "WP", "NN", "RB", "CC", "VBN", "RB", "CC", "VBD", "DT", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 689, "question": "Is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 690, "answer": "... for somebody who ate well and exercised well and did all the right things.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 702, "question": "Stunning, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 703, "answer": "It's really remarkable.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 723, "question": "And let's just ban, as Mayor Bloomberg has done in New York -- he's saying large product sales of that -- what do you think of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 724, "answer": "Well, the thing is, you know -- look, I'm not an expert on any of this.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Mayor Bloomberg"], "LOCATION": ["New York"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 729, "question": "But the fact that, you know, people are going to sort of now -- who wouldn't have paid attention before, are going to kind of sit up and go, Well, why would he want to do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "RB", ":", "WP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "NN", "IN", ",", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "CC", "VB", ",", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 730, "answer": "Right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["OK"]}, "docId": "120604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", ":", "CC", "RB", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 736, "question": "Any tips on anyone who -- anyone that wants to start a vegan diet now watching you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "WP", ":", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 737, "answer": "FEIFFER: Well, I would say what I did was I just said, OK, I'm just going to do -- I'm going to give myself eight weeks and I'm going to just -- I'm not going to commit to this for a lifetime because it's -- it's -- psychologically, it's huge for people to wrap their minds -- and just to see.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 749, "question": "But it also -- you know, it makes room for really interesting conversations now because they take me on, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 750, "answer": "They challenge you a little bit.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", ":"], "qSentId": 757, "question": "You like that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 758, "answer": "It's the first time I've done this...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJS", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "RB", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 810, "question": "Which of all these do you think the queen will be most excited by, Katie?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "IN", "DT", "DT", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "RBS", "VBN", "IN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 811, "answer": "Well, I think she was probably most excited by the pageant just because in her lifetime, as in ours, she would never have seen anything quite like that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Katie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 822, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 823, "answer": "I think absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120604pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 845, "question": "I mean, can you imagine?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 846, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]